<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Q_less</string>
    <string name="q_less_string">Q-Less.</string>
    <string name="asset_1">asset_1_3x_1</string>
    <string name="welcome_1_head">Streamline your mealtime</string>
    <string name="welcome_1_text">Say goodbye to long queues and waiting times.
                                With Q-Less, you can order your favorite meals ahead
                                of time and pick them up hassle-free.</string>
    <string name="welcome_2_head">Order from anywhere</string>
    <string name="welcome_2_text">Whether you\'re at home or on the go, our app lets
                                you browse menus and schedule pickups at your convenience.
                                Enjoy a seamless ordering experience every time.</string>
    <string name="welcome_3_head">Real-time updates</string>
    <string name="welcome_3_text">Receive instant notifications about order status,
                                pickup times, and exclusive deals. Spend less time
                                waiting and more time savoring delicious meals with Q-Less!</string>
    <string name="add_request">Add your request...</string>

    <!-- Strings for Restaurant 1 food list -->
    <string name="store1_menu1_title">Signature McYouTwit Burger</string>
    <string name="store1_menu1_description">Our signature burger featuring a juicy beef patty cooked to perfection, topped with melt…</string>
    <string name="store1_menu1_price">$12.80</string>

    <string name="store1_menu2_title">Signature McYouTwit Burger Combo</string>
    <string name="store1_menu2_description">Our mouthwatering signature burger paired  with a refreshing drink of your choice.</string>
    <string name="store1_menu2_price">$13.50</string>

    <string name="store1_menu3_title">Double Signature Burger Bundle</string>
    <string name="store1_menu3_description">Two mouthwatering signature burgers with your choice of sides. Perfect for sharing.</string>
    <string name="store1_menu3_price">$24.90</string>

    <string name="store1_menu4_title">Signature McYouTwit Fries in a Bucket</string>
    <string name="store1_menu4_description">Golden and crunchy on the outside, fluffy on the inside, and seasoned to perfection...</string>
    <string name="store1_menu4_price">$3.90</string>


    <!-- Strings for Restaurant 1 Menu 1 -->
    <string name="store1_menu1_full_description">Our signature burger featuring a juicy beef patty cooked to perfection, 
                                                topped with melted cheddar cheese, crisp lettuce, ripe tomatoes, caramelized onions, 
                                                and our secret special sauce, all sandwiched between a toasted brioche bun 
                                                for an unforgettable taste sensation.</string>


    <!-- Strings for Restaurant 2 - Malone's Cones-->
    <string name="store2_name">Malone\'s Cones</string>
    <string name="store2_rating">3.4</string>
    <string name="store2_pick_up">Pick up in 11 minutes</string>
    <string name="store2_distance">0.3km away</string>
    <string name="store2_address">5 Changi Business Park Central 1, Singapore 489343</string>

    <string name="store2_menu1_title">Special Super Scoop</string>

    <!-- String for Homepage -->
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_restaurant_info">RestaurantInfo</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"
    </string>

</resources>